You think about it, most people wouldn't
[music] stop to see a baby bird.
If they did, they'd just keep on going.
And this fell down.
>> I'll hold him [music] for a minute.
>> He's still alive. Yeah, he's good. You
can hear mom and dad up here. You see
him? It's a mockingbird. You know,
humans need to be kinder to nature.
You're a good woman. If you think about
it, they're animals just like us. Let me
to tell you. You think [music] Jesus
would leave a baby bird on the ground?
No, man.
He'd stop what he was doing and pick him
up. I love Alex so much because [music]
I can see the good in her by her
actions.
Okay.
All right.
If [music] we did nothing else today, it
would be a good day, wouldn't it?
Hey, that is what would Jesus do in
[music] action.